Guide to the Isidore Sydney Falk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1915-1977; Accession 1993-M-008; 2.5 linear feet (1 folio)
  Received from: Stephen Falk, 1992 July 22
  - Diplomas, awards, and certificates, 1915-1977 (Box 1)